I'm so glad you could finally take some
time off Bartleby
you've been on your business trip in
australia for so long
i was beginning to fear that you would
not be home in time for halloween my
lover
well to tell you the truth my i
decided to come home early
I'm supposed to be buying a 600 billion
dollar hotel in australia right now
but when you told me you were going to
the pumpkin patch to buy pumpkins
i just had to come along and watch it's
always a treat
observing how you poor people celebrate
your poor people holidays
[Music]
this looks like the perfect pumpkin for
carving what do you think Bartleby
Bartleby are you listening Bartleby are
you there
where did you go Bartleby my lover
oh yeah I'm listening my I just
have my eyes set on a couple of other
pumpkins right now
[Music]
haha what are you doing Bartleby those
aren't pumpkins those are my butt cheek
quit being silly I don't know about that
these look like some rather juicy
pumpkins too I'm almost tempted to keep
spanking them
until they get mashed into pumpkin puree
[Music]
remind me again why we are
painting these pumpkins as instead of
carving them
the poor person manual that I bought
last night says poor people usually
carve out pumpkin
haha I already told you Bartleby my mom
doesn't want me using a knife because
it's dangerous
that's right I forgot you poor people
are always such a treat to be era
it's cute how you have to worry about
getting hurt because you can't afford to
pay hospital bills
you